Okay, in terms of calls, generally when I need pricing urgently, I'll call the relevant supplier for the equipment.
As this generates the pricing or costing verbally via the call, it works out a lot faster in that route.
If it's not urgent, I generally email and then we follow up later on during the course of the day or the very next day.
So top three suppliers for valves, we're looking at valve specialist, MAC, Fluid, also EMV Africa.
And in this context too, it all depends what sort of valve, because each supplier has different unique suppliers of valves for themselves.
Also for the hydraulics, I look at mainly one supplier, hydro systems, as they generally are very knowledgeable and they give me one of the best prices.
But also in the same context, they don't do hydraulic filtration systems, they don't do hydraulic quick couplers.
So this I have to get from a different supplier, which is hydro sales.
Suppliers I wish I had, obviously this generally comes up only when it's equipment that I haven't dealt with.
Most of the equipment I deal with is all familiar to me, so I don't think I have any supplies I would want to put on as yet.