Okay, so KG Engineering is a specialist company that services your manufacturing industries,
your agricultural industries, anything to do with repairs and maintenance of valves, pneumatics,
hydraulics, boilers, LPG gas lines, all industrial aspects of your manufacturing process.
We can assist with supply of material, installation of material and also refurbishment of material.
Inquiries are generated via site visits mainly, but obviously we would still like to look
into websites and referrals.
So what eats up most of my time is invoicing statements and also following up on quotations
from suppliers as this is very time-consuming calls, emails, regularly, WhatsApps as well
to suppliers, then also follow-ups to clients regarding quotes submitted and projects submitted
as well.
Things that frustrate me the most would be not issuing out statements and invoices
on time as this eats away cash flow and it's always delayed on my side as there's quite
a bit going on in the background.
So the software that I currently use now is Zoho invoicing software and also WhatsApp
for client.
Clients contact me directly via WhatsApp if they need me to come to site or even quote
on items they are fully understood about what they require.
Usually a typical job goes like this, we go to site, we generate the inquiry, we come
back, we do research, if research is needed on items that we are not familiar with, we
quote and then we either supply or we onsite with the installation work.