show me show me show me you just sent you it's working fine you just sent me an
email just now I attached it in an email where you were saying you are
building the database for me and I am just asking you to not send it to my
email because you are not building the database for me you are building it for
my husband I have sent to my husband's email I said just send it to him the same
way you just did few minutes ago hasn't even been like 10 minutes since you
did you done that you can then come back and tell me it's not working it makes
no sense unless you are just trying to chow my tokens and frustrate me by
send packing of which I'm not gonna play that game please send this email to my
husband's email kgengineeringpumps at jmail.com