No, I still want to continue today, but on a different project, a French new project
all together.
So this is why I'm saying let's pack the AutoSight SA, CHOMI AI project for now.
I want to start an automation project, which is now a new different project that maybe
we can list in under CHOMI as well.
I don't know.
So here's where we are.
My husband, Darren Amilchand, has a business.
It's KG Engineering.
I'm going to just give him the phone so he can just stamp.
As much information as in terms of what the business does, what he does, all the bits
that he does like for the business to keep it running from making phone calls, quotations,
all the bits, because I don't have intimate information of all of that.
And then from there, you and myself can figure out how we can automate some of the bits that
he does.